▍2026 辛辛那提 ATP1000 第三轮
菲斯 6-1 6-7(7) 6-3 莱赫奇卡 · 赛后场上采访
our tour congratulations I reckon
祝贺你啊
this must be your biggest win
这应该是你最大的一场胜利
since the injury since coming back
自从伤愈复出以来
is this you saying here I am I'm back
是不是在说 我回来了？
yeah honestly I think that was one
是啊 说实话 我觉得这是
of the toughest match I play very happy
我打过最艰难的一场 很开心
with the win today I mean we I
拿下今天这场 我是说
think we played some great tennis
我们都打出了很好的网球
and some tough condition you know
条件也不容易 你知道
the boys a bit flying
球有点飘
but very happy with the way I close it was
但我很满意收官的方式 挺好
very tough I mean he had break points I
很艰难 他有破发点 我也有
had break points happy to to take it today
破发点 今天能拿下很开心
the match point at the end
第二盘结尾那个赛点
of the second set tell us the story
跟我们说说
of that and what happened thereafter
当时发生了什么 后来又怎样
you know I mean at least I went
你知道 至少我
for it okay I miss a little bit but I played
出手了 打偏了一点 但我是带着
with with my conviction just didn't go
自己的判断打的 只是没进
through it's okay then I
没关系 那样的话
would be way more angry if I'm missing
我会更生气 如果我是打丢网
the net or if I don't create anything I went
或者根本没制造机会 我出手了
for it I miss it it's okay let's go
打丢了 没关系 再来
for another one
拼一个
and I think I did it pretty good
我觉得自己做得还不错
I reckon this is nine deciding sets this year
这是你今年第九个决胜盘
you know how many you've won right
知道自己赢了几个吗
nine wins nine wins out of nine
九场全赢 九战九胜
there's the wink okay what does that say
看你眨眼了 这说明
about you
什么
let's say
这么说吧
that I'm very good competitor I guess
我是个很不错的斗士 我猜
and when I find a way if I find a way
只要我找到办法 找到办法
to win one set why not two sets I mean
赢下一盘 为什么不能两盘
come on even though we are once
拜托 哪怕我们战成一比一
at all I know what I did to win the first set
我也知道怎么赢下第一盘
so I'm gonna win this third set
所以这第三盘我也会赢
great stuff today you got some autograph
今天打得漂亮 你还有签名
to sign I think well done
要签 干得好
yeah thank you very much
是啊 非常感谢